I found a love for me
Darling, just die right in
Follow my lead
I found a girl
Beautiful and sweet
I never knew you were
The someone waiting for me
Because we were just kids when we fell in love
Not knowing what it was
I will not give you up
This time
Darling, just kiss me slow
Your heart is all I own
And in your eyes, you're old in mine
Baby, I'm dancing in the dark
With you between my arms
Barefoot on the cross
Listening to our favorite song
When you said you looked at me
I whispered underneath my breath
You heard it, darling
You look perfect tonight
Well, I found a woman
Stronger than anyone I know
She shares my dreams I hold
And someday I'll share her home
I found a love
To carry more than just my secrets
To carry love and to carry children of our own
We are still kids, but we're so in love
Fighting against all odds
I know we'll be alright
This time
Darling, just hold my hand
We're gonna be your men
I'll sing a future in the eye
Baby, I'm dancing in the dark
With you between my arms
Barefoot on the cross
Listening to our favorite song
When I saw you in that dress
Looking so beautiful
I don't deserve this
Darling, you look perfect tonight
Darling, you look perfect
Baby, I'm dancing in the dark
With you between my arms
Barefoot on the cross
Listening to our favorite song
When I have faith in what I see
Now I know I have met an angel
In person
She looks perfect
I don't deserve this
You look perfect tonight
I'm dancing in the dark